A sound soul, dwells within a sound mind, and a sound body.
R-Run away! The Black Dragon! The Black Dragon is here!
You have no idea.
Where are you from?
No, no.
roll it down, I kind of pregunt.
Oh no!
END
繋いだ魂の火が胸を刺すなら 言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか
六人目も合わさず 運命まで絡んでく 行き先もらったポテル 食えない夜の端で
不可愛しすぎた眩しさが 悪い夢に続いても
繋いだ魂の火が胸を刺すなら 言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか
やっと理由は永遠に 突きつけられて
触れた瞬間の傷の分だけ 確かになれる
Row, row, row, row, just gently down the street
Come on, can't you row any faster?
Will you explain to me what we're doing in a rowboat in the first place?
Why not a motorboat or a nice big cruise ship?
You know, something with an engine maybe?
Quit complaining
Anyway, we've almost reached our destination now
That's where we're going?
That's a nice enough looking village, I guess. Seems pretty peaceful
I'm not so sure about that
Why? The place looks okay to me
Look over there
What the heck happened?
A few days ago, the people who lived here were swallowed up by something
Along with their homes?
Please don't tell me we're here to find out what was responsible
Let's go
We need to gather information
Can you tell me what happened here?
It was the mist
Mist?
What do you mean? What kind of mist?
No, no
Calm down
Don't worry, you're alright now
We're here to help you
We've come from the DWMA to put a stop to whatever did this
The Academy?
Yes
So please tell me in as much detail as you can what happened here
Black... Black Dragon
The Black Dragon came
The Black Dragon came and ate our village
Black Dragon
Interesting
The Soul-Eating Black Dragon
Scaredy Cat Liz and her merry friends
Elephant
Chimpanzee
Dog
Cat
Very good
for picture books let me guess a pigeon yeah and that was a pig come on kid tell me we're done with
this musty old place it's suffocating in here don't be such a slacker preliminary research
is necessary which is what I would tell you if I didn't hate this place too I think I've got
enough basic information let's go we need to get started good so then what's our next destination
you can row harder than that can't you
why are we back in this stupid rowboat whatever we're going to do it better be real important
or else of course it is would I make you work this hard for nothing well knowing you yes so
what is this black dragon thing we're after this part of the Baltic Sea is a key maritime area there
has been a lot of boat traffic out here sailors have been crossing these waters since the Vikings
first set sail okay but what does that have to do with some scary black dragon not every boat makes
it to shore so in an area where there are many ships crossing that means there are also a number of ships
sinking oh kid I don't think I like where this is heading just because a ship sinks doesn't mean it'll stay sunk
what is this it's missed what kind of missed we're getting close stay sharp what I sense the presence of
the king with countless numbers of souls in this area it means that's the black dragon see that writing
Nidhogg?
Nidhogg is the name of a black dragon that appears in Norse mythology.
According to the legend, it's also the name of a ghost ship that haunts these waters.
Many people have believed the legend to be true.
And now I can see why they would.
Right! Ladies, let's go! We're heading up there!
There's no way! Not a chance! It's a ghost ship!
Which means there's gonna be ghosts on it!
Run!
Wait, honey! Honey, honey, honey!
You idiot! I told you to wait, didn't I?
Whoopsie! Sorry.
If you want to do damage to the other ship, you have to ram them in the middle!
You're mad because she didn't hit the middle?
Now do it again!
Okay!
Bro!
Okay, let's board.
You guys are absolutely crazy!
Worse than crazy!
You're insane crazy jerks!
Insane crazy jerks with a death wish!
Oh, no!
I was so busy focusing on their insanity that I came on board! I'm gonna die!
From what I'm sensing, the souls are inside the ship somewhere. In we go.
Yeah.
Oh, I've got a better idea. How about we don't?
There are ghosts hanging around in there, remember?
What if they eat us?
Hey, guys, are you listening to me?
You guys!
Let's go, Liz.
A fresh batch of souls have come to me all on their own.
They're just ahead.
All these human souls.
Whatever someone has planned, it isn't good.
Can we take all these souls because they don't belong to anyone?
Idiot!
Do you want to become a Kishan?
As a protector of souls, I can't allow this.
I have to safeguard them.
What do we have here?
You're a Krim Reaper?
Liz.
Paddy.
Yeah, okay.
Pay!
Lead hard!
Liz, wait!
She fell!
She's your sister! How could you be laughing like that?
This ship is my body and my body is this ship!
All I have to do is digest the little lady!
Are you an evil spirit?
What are you planning to do with all these human souls you've gathered?
The meddlesome Lord Death is making things more difficult for me than ever before.
That's why I'm going to present these souls to the Kishan.
I'll certainly be rewarded for that.
Kishan?
You mean the sword Ragnarok?
That rookie doesn't have anything to do with this.
No, no, I'm talking about the Kishan who's right next to you.
That's who I gathered these souls for.
What's that? What do you mean next to us?
It's nothing a child like you would understand.
This ship and I have things to do, people to see.
We're going places together, me and this ship.
Somewhere at sea far away, people are waiting to hear the song of the Kishan.
Most people are alike.
They all crave power in one form or another.
But for some, no amount of earthly power will ever be enough to satisfy.
They always hunger for more.
It's humans like these who are seeking the Kishan.
And these souls that you see here are my own offering to it.
They're not for you, boys!
Hey kid, I'm gonna transform now.
No.
I can't.
I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't do this!
Paddy? Kid? Where are you?
I hope the ghosts haven't eaten you.
Kid won't be able to use Paddy without me.
It would be asymmetrical, he'd get a nosebleed and pass out.
There's no way they'll be able to fight whatever's on this creepy ship.
I have to get back to them quickly.
Okay!
I'm not the least bit frightened! No way is this ghost ship scary to me!
I'm one of the Thompson sisters, the legendary devils of Brooklyn
nobody wants to run into in a dark alley!
Nothing frightens me!
Nothing!
What am I doing on the ship out of this oven to me?
Just our luck that we went and mugged a grim reaper!
Life isn't fair!
Where am I going?
Is this even the right way?
Yes it is. This way.
This way!
Hey thanks, that's very nice of you.
Who said that?
I'm just hearing things, that's all.
You're doing well. Just keep coming straight this way!
I won't look! I won't look! I won't look! I won't look! I won't look! If I don't look she'll go away!
No one's there! No one's there! No one's there! No one's there! Oh please let no one be there! I won't look!
Come on! Just a little further this way!
Help me!
I'm the spirit of a girl who was eaten by this ship! Don't worry! I'm not going to hurt you!
I'm not dumb! I know how ghosts work! You were eaten and now you're angry and restless and you have revenge so you're going to eat me!
I don't have any reason to eat you. I only want to help you. If you'll just follow me I can take you back to your friends, okay?
I can see through you! You're lying! You want to gobble up my hot body!
No, I'm not going to eat you. You just have to trust me.
I might have big boobs but I'm all skin and bones! Just trust me.
I'd be stringy and tough and not tasty at all! I promise!
Just trust me!
Okay, that's enough! Quit your talus blathering and follow me right now!
Or I'll fake you to death!
Yes ma'am, I'll follow you anywhere!
I'm glad we got that straightened out. Now get moving!
Crying out loud, I don't see what you have to be so upset about anyway. I didn't even get to live long enough to have a hot body like you.
Oh yeah, I'm sorry I rubbed it in really. Patty, your big sis ain't doing so well!
Runnin' away won't do any good!
I partnered with these two specifically so something like this wouldn't happen! I need symmetry. Maybe I should have listened to my father. He tried to pick out a good weapon for me, but I refused to listen to him.
Stubborn!
All I cared about, all I wanted, was symmetry! Two symmetrical weapons! Was that so much to ask for? And now all my efforts.
Have been completely and utterly wasted!
Dammit!
Where did this go?
Tammit!
Wasted
Where did this go hey this way come this way
What's the matter boy shouldn't the Grim Reaper have more power than this you haven't seen what I can do yet
Then why not show me something are you frightened Reaper boy?
I worship the keys in your sworn enemy and I steal the souls of innocent people
This is the perfect chance to pass judgment on what you call evil
I do not deny evil nor do I believe that any human is completely free of malice
Everything must be in balance as long as evil and good maintain an equilibrium in this world. There is no problem
Perfect balance is the key to everything
For one second that all humans feel the same way you do I don't care if they do or not
I'm going to keep fighting until this world is the way it should be until the world is balanced
Really even if that means taking away freedom you disgust me. Yeah, I am a Grim Reaper. I refuse to grant anyone the freedom to kill
Come this way
This is the way
Here we are
No, thanks a lot for all your help
We're up on deck all right, but I don't see anybody else
I knew if I was right all along you are going to eat me. You're going to simmer me in a pot with onions and garlic and have me for dinner. I'm running right now. Don't cry or I will smack you
I will smack you
Oh, hi sis
Hey there, Liz. Nice of you to show up. You idiots because of you. I couldn't use Patty. You know that
It's not my fault that you're crazy
You're back
Patty
I missed you so much
You aren't going to get away
Finally now that we're all back together. We can take care of business. Liz Patty time to transform. Let's go
Hey
Yeah, okay
Time to die
Yeah
What was that?
The sword
Ragnarok
Scream resonance
What the?
The swords are coming out now
Ragnarok
I have to go
Goodbye, dumb scaredy cat lady
Ragnarok
O neck
Lagnarok
Ragnarok
this can't be possible he devoured all of the human souls you must have been real hungry huh
you bastard
i think we're looking at the demon sword's true form
hey you're achy and gross
what is he there's nothing human about that thing up there
in this region of the baltic sea there was once a legend believed by many about a ghost ship called
the black dragon however this thing in front of us this demon sword
is a true black dragon
hey my blood is black you know
i judge you
reaper combat art mortal sin stance
it's time to die
you
Thank you.
On the next episode of Soul Eater, fierce battle aboard the ghost ship, the hell inside my head.